Morty, hurry!
Return the Truth Tortoise!
Morty, whatever you do,
don't drop the Truth Tortoise!
Also really important,
whatever you do,
don't look into its eyes!
I... I did look at it, Rick!
I've been looking at it!
Now you're gonna know
everything, Morty!
Good job! Way to go!
You [bleep] everything up!
[ Speaking gibberish ]
It's in my head!
[ Screams ]
Ah!
Oh, geez, I... I can't get that
Truth Tortoise out of my head.
Yeah, I told you not
to look into its eyes.
Hey, Morty, let's watch some
interdimensional cable.
Remember how we used to do that?
Rick, I can't...
I can't go on.
I-I can't go on like this with the
Truth Tortoise shit in my head.
I-I wish you could just...
Erase the memory from your mind?
How did you know
I was gonna say that?
Come on, Morty, come with me.
After you.
What the hell is this?!
This, Morty, is my archive
of all the experiences
you've begged me to remove